[
{
        "question": "من الشخصية ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛👦🏻🪀⚡❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "كيلوا"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "من الشخصية ❍˚┊❛👦🏻🗡️☀️🔥❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "فيتان"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "من الشخصية ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛🐜👑❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "ميريوم"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "من الشخصية ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛👦🏻🦯❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "غون"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "من الشخصية ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛👩🏻👓🕷️❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "شيزوكو"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "من الشخصية ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛👦🏻👁️⛓️❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "كورابيكا"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "من الشخصية ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛🃏🃏🕷️❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "هيسوكا"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "من الشخصية ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛👑👒❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "لوفي"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "من الشخصية ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛👩🏻🙏🏻🙌🏻❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "روبين"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "من الشخصية ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛💉🦌 ❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "تشوبر"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "من الشخصية ❍˚┊❛👱🏼‍♂️🗡️⚔️🧭 ❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "زورو"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "من الشخصية ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛💀🎻❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "بروك"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "من الشخصية ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛👩🏻🌩️🏑❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "نامي"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "من الشخصية ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛🐟💪🏻🌊❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "جينبي"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "من الشخصية ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛🤥🌱💣❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "اوسوب"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "من الشخصية ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛👩🏻💘🗻❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "هانكوك"
    } ,
 {
        "question": "من الشخصية ❍˚┊❛👱🏼‍♂️🕶️🛡️🤖❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "فرانكي"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "من الشخصية ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛👨🏼‍🍳🤸🏼‍♂️🚬❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "سانجي"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "من الشخصية ❍- ͙۪۪̥˚┊❛👱🏼‍♂️🎩🔥❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "سابو"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "من الشخصية ❍˚┊❛🐲🧔🏻‍♂☠️❜┊˚ ͙۪۪̥",
        "response": "كايدو"
    }
     
]
